Register of the Elizabeth Churchill Brown Papers 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILES, 1837-1984
  - Communism
    - Entertainment. Clippings, memoranda, miscellany, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, resports, hearing transcripts, 1950-1980
      - AWARE, Inc. (Folder 5)
        - Correspondence with J. Edgar Hoover and others, 1953-1955
    - Internal security (subversive activities). Biographical sketches, clippings, hearing transcripts, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, serial issues, speech transcripts, statements, reports, reprints, 1942-1980
      - General (Folder 6)
        - Correspondence with Martin Dies. Includes a mimeographed copy of a statement by Michael A. Musmanno relating to outlawing the Communist party, 1954
        - Non-printed material, 1954
        - Printed material. Newsletters, hearing transcripts, 1950-1974
      - Espionage. Hearing transcripts and newsletters, 1952-1978 (Folder 7)
      - Individuals. Biographical sketches, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, statements, transcripts, 1942-1980.
        (NOTE: This material relates generally to alleged subversive activities or associations)
        - General
          - General. (Reference to more than one individual). Newsletters, reports, 1958-1973 (Folder 8)
          - Institute of Pacific Relations. Excerpts from testimony, list, correspondence with Ezra Benson, 1951-1955. (Folder 9)
        - Adler, Solomon, n.d. (Folder 10)
        - Atkinson, Brooks, n.d.
        - Attlee, Clement, 1949
        - Beam, Jacob D., 1969
        - Bethune, Mary McLeod, 1952-1953
        - Browder, Earl and Raissa. SEE ALSO: CORRESPONDENCE/Browder, Earl and Raissa
          - General. Clippings, newsletters, notes, reports, and typescript copy of Duane Thorin, Browder's Marx Chowder, 1943-1973 (Folder 11)
          - Speeches and writings, 1943-1960 (Folder 12)
            - America's Changing Foreign Policy, Printed article, 1959.
            - The Future of the Anglo-Soviet-American Coalition, Reprint, 1943.
            - Karl Marx and America, Mimeographed pamphlet with typescript draft, 1957.
            - Socialism in America, Printed pamphlet, 1960.
            - Teheran: Our Path in War and Peace, Paperback book, 1944.
        - Buchanan, Frank, 1951 (Folder 13)
        - Budenz, Louis, 1950
        - Caplin, Jerome Benton, 1958
        - Celler, Emanuel, 1954-1964
        - Chaplin, Charles, 1942-1950
        - Chapman, Oscar L., 1950
        - Coplon, Judith, 1965
        - Crouch, Paul. Correspondence and mimeographed statement, 1954-1955
        - Currie, Lauchlin, 1961
        - Davies, John Paton, c. 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Dodd, Bella, 1954
        - Douglas, Paul H. (Senator). Mimeographed list of participation in subversive organizations, 1951
        - Epstein, Israel, n.d.
        - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1955
        - Forman, Harrison, n.d.
        - Furry, Wendell H., 1954
        - Gayn, Mark J., 1945
        - Hammer, Armand, 1969
        - Hawkins, Augustus Freeman, 1975
        - Hemenway, John, 1973
        - Hughes, Langston, c. 1962
        - Jessup, Philip. Notes, memorandum, mimeographed report from Joe McCarthy, Documentary Evidence on Philip C. Jessup, Ambassador-at-Large, 1951 (Folder 2)
        - Josephson, Emanuel, 1965 (Folder 3)
        - Jowitt, (Lord), n.d.
        - Kamin, Leon J., 1954
        - Kilgore, Harley (Senator). Pamphlet, The Red Record of Senator Harvey Kilgore, c. 1952
        - Lamont, Corliss, 1954
        - Lattimore, Owen. Clippings, excerpts from testimony, press releases, statements by Thomas Dodd and Patrick McCarran, report, 1953-1972 (Folder 4)
        - Lovestone, Jay, SEE ALSO: SPEECHES AND WRITINGS/Articles and speeches/, 1954. 1961
        - Ludden, Raymond
        - Matusow, Harvey Marshall
          - General. Press releases, statements, 1951-1955 (Folder 5)
          - Senate Internal Security subcommittee investigation, Strategy and Tactics of World Communism, 1955
            - Hearing transcripts, Parts 1-11, 1955 (Folder 6-9)
            - Report, 1955 (Folder 10)
        - Norman, Edgerton Herbert. Clippings, newsletters, printed articles, testimony transcript summary, 1951-1957 (Folder 11)
        - Peress, Irving, Senate Internal Security subcommittee investigation, Army Personnel Actions Relating to Irving Peress, 1955.
          - Hearings transcripts, Parts 1-7, 1955 (Folder 12-14)
          - Report, 1955
        - Perlo, Victor, n.d. (Folder 15)
        - Posniak, Edward G. Clipping, notes, serial issue, mimeographed copy of FBI report, 1948-1968
        - Pound, Ezra, 1958
        - Robeson, Paul, Includes reports relating to the Peekskill demonstrations of 1949 Aug.-Sept., 1949-1958. (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Roth, Andrew
        - Service, John. Includes statement before Senate Subcommittee on Foreign Relations, 1945-1950 (Folder 2)
        - Starobin, Joseph R., 1954
        - Stern, Martha and Alfred, 1979-1980
        - Unger, Abraham, 1954
        - Wallach, Erica, 1958
        - Williams, Aubrey, n.d.
        - Zborowski, Mark, 1959
      - Investigative Committees
        - General. Correspondence with Sidney W. Souers, 1949 (Folder 3)
        - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1952-1973 (Folder 4)
          - Correspondence with J. Edgar Hoover and Francis P. Walter, 1957-1959
          - General. List of publications, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, radio broadcast transcripts, 1954-1973
        - Internal Security Subcommittee, U.S. Senate. Mimeographed copies of hearing transcripts, press releases, 1953-1957
          - Interlocking Subversion in Government Departments, 1953-1955 (Folder 5)
          - Scope of Soviet Activity in the United States, 1956-1957 (Folder 6-7)
            - Press releases, 1956-1957
            - Transcripts, 1957
      - Smith Act. Form letter, newsletter, 1956 (Folder 8)
      - State Department. Clippings, correspondence, printed hearing transcripts and reports, newsletters, press releases, reprints, 1952-1976
        - General. Clippings, hearing transcripts, newsletters, pamphlets and printed copy (pamphlet) issued by Joe McCarthy (?), The Party of Betrayal, 1952-1966 (Folder 9-10)
        - Otepka, Otto (Folder 11)
          - General. Clippings, newsletters, reprints, 1963-1976
          - Correspondence, 1969-1971
      - Subversive Activities Control Board. Briefs, reports and mimeographed copy of Harry P. Cain, Can Freedom Live with Internal Security?, 1955-1959 (Folder 12-13)
    - Labor
      - General. Correspondence, miscellany, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, reports, 1951-1981 (Folder 14)
      - Reuther, Walter. Clippings, correspondence with Joseph Kamp, newsletters, notes, 1952-1967 (Folder 15)
    - Medicine (Box 21)
      - General. Newsletter and correspondence with Robert P. Hudson and Errett P. Scriver, 1958-1959 (Folder 1)
      - Fluoridation. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, 1954-1964 (Folder 2)
      - Mental health. Clippings, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, reports, reprints, transcripts, 1944-1965
        - General. American Public Relations Forum, Speaker's kit on mental health. Flyers, pamphlets and reprints, 1944-1961 (Folder 3)
        - Correspondence with J.B. Matthews, National Association for Mental Health (NAMH), William Sargant, Boris Sokoloff, George F. Sutherland, Irene Traffert and others, 1959-1960 (Folder 4-5)
        - Non-printed material, Includes typescript copies of Boris Sokoloff, The Scientific Basis of Soviet Efforts for the Control of Human Behavior, Charles Stickley, Brain-washing: A Synthesis of the Text - Book on Psychopolitics, and a mimeographed memorandum, National Association for Mental Health, Inc., Analysis of Criticism of the Mental Health Movement and NAMH, 1954-1959. 1954; 1955; 1959 (Folder 6)
        - Printed material, Includes printed copies of G.B. Chisholm, The Psychiatry of Enduring Peace and Social Progress (serial issue), the World Federation of Mental Health, Mental Health and World Citizenship, and Lewis Albert Alesen, Mental Robots, 1946-1963. 1946; 1948; 1957 (Folder 7-8)
      - Individual cases
        - Bartholomew, Fletcher. Transcript of radio broadcast, 1958 (Folder 9)
        - Rogers, Senta. Correspondence, forms, memoranda, statment, 1955-1958 (Folder 10)
        - Seelig, Fred. Newsletter, 1965 (Folder 11)
        - Winston, Robert A. Correspondence with James O. Eastland, press release, statement, 1960
    - New Left (Box 22)
      - General. Clippings, newsletters, notes, press releases, reprints, 1960-1982
        - Non-printed material, 1960-1976 (Folder 1)
        - Printed material, Includes copies of the Washington Free Press and the Quicksilver Times, 1960-1982. (Folder 2)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (Folder 3)
        - Correspondence. Mrs. Irene Traffert, 1960-1961
        - General. Newsletters, 1956-1974
      - American Indian Movement. Newsletter, 1973 (Folder 4)
      - Anti-nuclear movement. Newsletter, 1977 (Folder 5)
      - Anti-war (Vietnam) movement. Clippings, flyers, newsletters, FBI (?) reports, 1965-1972 (Folder 6)
      - Black movements
        - General
          - General. Flyers, form letters, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, reprints, and mimeographed copy of J.B. Matthews, Communists, Negroes and Integration, 1954-1974 (Folder 7-8)
          - Civil disorder
            - General. Chart, newsletters, press releases, 1964-1971 (Folder 9)
            - Printed report by the National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, One Year Later, SEE ALSO: AUDIOVISUAL FILE, 1968. (Folder 10)
        - Civil rights
          - General (Folder 11)
            - General. Correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, 1957-1971
            - King, Martin Luther, Jr. Form letters, newsletters, 1968-1978 (Folder 12)
          - Desegregation. Clippings, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, reports (FBI?), and correspondence with a mimeographed copy of report by Carleton Putnam, 1954-1965 (Folder 13)
        - Nationalism. Clippings, form letters, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, serial issues, transcripts, 1965-1977 (Box 23)
          - Non-printed material, 1965-1976 (Folder 1)
          - Printed material, 1965-1977 (Folder 2-3)
      - Chicanos and farm workers. Clippings, flyers, newsletters, programs, 1966-1976. (Folder 4)
      - Communist Party. Form letters, newsletters, reports (FBI?), transcripts, 1958-1971
        - Non-printed material, 1967-1971 (Folder 5)
        - Printed material, 1958-1970 (Folder 6)
      - Intellectuals. Correspondence, conference proceedings and programs, newsletters, reports, reprints, telegrams, 1952-1973
        - General, 1952-1973 (Folder 7)
          - Non-printed material. Mimeographed memoranda, 1952-1957
          - Printed material, 1961-1973
        - Pugwash Conference. Proceedings and printed report, 1961-1964 (Folder 8)
        - Socialist Scholars Conferences. Program, printed newsletters and pamphlets, 1967-1971
      - Morality. Clippings, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, transcripts, 1956-1983 (Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1959-1962
        - General, 1956-1983
      - Prison movements. Newsletters, 1971 (Folder 10)
      - Puerto Rican movements. Newsletters, 1974-1977 (Folder 11)
      - Revolutionary terrorism. Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, 1970-1979 (Folder 12)
      - Students. Clippings, correspondence, flyers, press releases, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, reports, transcripts, 1952-1970
        - General (Folder 13)
          - General, 1952-1970
          - Correspondence. Edward O. Weant, Jr., 1967
        - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS). Newsletters, reports, transcripts, 1965-1970 (Folder 14)
      - Venceremos Brigade. Form letter, c. 1971 (Folder 15)
    - Propaganda. Correspondence, flyers, form letters, newsletters, pamphlets, posters, serial issue (U.S.S.R. Information Bulletin, Includes mimeographed copy of Suzanne Labin, The Technique of Soviet Propaganda, and typescript photocopy (FBI?), Communists Aim Propaganda at Farmers, 1952), 1946-1983. 1959; n.d. (Folder 16-17)
    - Religion (Box 24)
      - Correspondence with the Committee of Christian Laymen, Inc., Thomas J. Dodd, Clare Boothe Luce, Carl McIntire, the United States Information Agency, and others, 1956-1976 (Folder 1-3)
      - Non-printed material. Articles, notes, press releases, resolutions, statements, transcripts, 1936-1976 (Folder 4)
      - Printed material. Clippings and typescript copies of articles (some translated from Italian), newsletters, pamphlets, reports, reprints, transcripts, 1950-1984
        - General, 1954-1971 (Folder 5)
        - Newsletters, 1957-1984 (Folder 6)
          - General, 1957-1969
          - Committee of Christian Laymen, Inc. Also includes non-printed progress reports
            - #1-100, 1962 April 1-1964 June 10 (Folder 7)
            - #101-150, 1964 June 11-1966 Dec. 1 (Folder 8)
            - #151-198, 1967 Jan. 3-1970 Sept. 22 (Folder 9)
            - Progress reports, 1963-1970 (Folder 10)
          - Mindszenty Report, 1965-1984 (Folder 11)
        - Pamphlets, 1950-1973
          - General, 1952-1973 (Folder 12-14)
          - McIntire, Carl, 1950-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Strategy and tactics. Clippings, correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reprints, transcripts, SEE ALSO: Communism/Internal Security/Individuals/Matusow, Harvey Marshall, 1951-1975.
      - International. Clippings, newsletters and letter from Karlis Kalnins to Gamal Abdel Nasser, 1951-1971 (Folder 2)
      - United States
        - General. Newsletters and pamphlets, 1956-1975 (Folder 3)
        - Cultural exchange. Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, 1958-1966 (Folder 4)
  - Congo (Katanga). Newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, statement by Thomas J. Dodd, transcripts, and correspondence with Suzanne and Edouard Labin, 1960-1965 (Folder 5)
  - Cuba. Biographical sketches, correspondence, memoranda, naval communications, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reprints, transcripts, wire reports, 1954-1978
    - General. Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Folder 6)
    - Foreign relations
      - General. Biographical sketch, newsletters, conference addresses by J.E. de la Torriente, and Guillermo Martinez Marquez, conference reports, the Inter-American Press Association, Report of the Special Committee on Cuba, and Eudocio Ravines, Free Cubans Present a Challenge to Washington, and printed copy (pamphlet) of Osvaldo Dorticos Torrado, The Revolution has Not Betrayed Cuba but Has Fulfilled its Ideals, 1960-1973 (Folder 7)
      - U.S.S.R. (Folder 8)
      - United States
        - General. Newsletters, serial issue (Carib), speech transcripts and printed copies (pamphlets) issued by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Republic of Cuba, The Position of Cuban Sugar in the United States, and another pamphlet denouncing Cuban-American intervention in the leaflet raid of Oct. 21, 1959 (in French), 1959-1978 (Folder 9-10)
        - Bay of Pigs. Typescript rough draft of article, n.d. (Folder 11)
        - Missile crisis. Wire reports, newsletter, pamphlets, mimeographed speech transcript of John F. Kennedy, The Offensive Military Build-up on Cuba, and a printed copy (pamphlet) of Duane Thorin, The Cuban Crisis and the Grand Design, 1962-1963 (Folder 12)
    - Internal affairs. Printed copies of Internal Security committee reports, 1962-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Czechoslovakia. Printed copy of Joseph C. Whelan, Aspects of Intellectual Ferment and Dissent in Czechoslovakia, 1969 (Folder 14)
  - Defense. Bibliographies, biographical sketches, clippings, correspondence, flyers, maps, memoranda, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, transcripts, 1950-1982
    - General
      - General
        - Non-printed material. Includes remarks by Styles Bridges, William E. Jenner, Phyllis Schlafly, and Charles A. Willoughby, 1957-1972 (Folder 15)
        - Printed material, 1958-1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence with Styles Bridges, Daniel J. Flood, Alfred Kohlberg, John E. Moss, National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, and others, 1957-1958 (Folder 2)
    - Armed Forces. Bibliographies, biographical sketches, flyers, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, reports, reprints, transcripts, 1950-1977
      - General
        - General, 1950-1977 (Folder 3)
        - Communist infiltration, Includes correspondence and printed copy of Hamilton A. Long, America's Tragedy Today, 1950-1972. 1950. (Folder 4)
        - Status of Forces Treaty, 1957
      - Navy, Includes testimony transcript and mimeographed report by Admiral Arleigh Burke Regarding the Military Posture of the United States Navy, 1958-1975. c. 1960 (Folder 5-6)
    - Arms control. Memoranda, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, transcripts, 1955-1982
      - General
        - Non-printed material. Mimeographed copies of statements by Phyllis Schlafly, Lawrence H. Smith, Arthur G. Trudeau, and Duane Thorin, 1957-1967 (Folder 7)
        - Printed material. Includes transcript of a speech by N. Khrushchev before the United Nations General Assembly, The Soviet Union Proposes General and Complete Disarmament of all Nations, 1955-1982 (Folder 8-9)
      - Treaties. Pamphlets, press releases, newsletters, transcripts, 1959-1974
        - General, 1964-1972 (Folder 10)
        - Nuclear Test Ban Treaty. Includes mimeographed statements by Thomas J. Dodd and Lewis L. Strauss, and a mimeographed copy of the United States Information Service report, The Nuclear Test Ban Treaty: Gateway to Peace, 1959-1963 (Folder 11)
        - Strategic Arms Limitations Treaties (I and II), 1972-1974 (Folder 12)
    - Civil defense. Correspondence, maps, pamphlets, 1959-1967 (Folder 13)
    - Civil-Military relations. Newsletters, 1960-1968
      - General (Folder 14)
      - Reports
        - Thorin, Duane, The Need for Civil Authority over the Military, Printed copy with typescript drafts, 1968. (Folder 15)
        - Waskow, Arthur I. Quis Custodiet? Controlling the Peace in a Disarmed World, Peace Research Institute Report with appendices, 1963. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Congress. Newsletters, reports, transcripts, 1961-1976
      - General, c. 1965-1976 (Folder 2)
      - Thurmond, Strom. Newsletters, press releases, reports, transcripts, 1961-1965 (Folder 3-4)
    - Defense Department, Biographical sketches, newsletters, reports and correspondence with William C. Foster. Includes mimeographed copy of Committee on the Defense Establishment, Report to Senator Kennedy, 1951-1975. c. 1960 (Folder 5)
      - General. Clippings, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, reports, reprints, transcripts, wire reports, 1956-c. 1965 (Folder 6)
        - General. Includes President's Committee on Scientists and Engineers, Final Report to the President, 1957-1958
        - Trudeau, Arthur G., Chief of Research and Development for the Army. Clippings, printed pamphlets and reprints, mimeographed copies of radio broadcast and speech transcripts, SEE ALSO: CORRESPONDENCE/Trudeau, Arthur G., 1956-c. 1965. (Folder 7-8)
      - Internal security. Clippings, correspondence, newsletters, notes, 1949-1964
        - General, 1954-1964 (Folder 9)
        - Condon, Edward U., 1954
        - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1949-1963 (Folder 10)
        - Struik, Dirk J., 1949-1956
      - Space. Newsletter and pamphlet, 1957. (Folder 11)
      - Weapons systems. Clippings, newsletters, notes, press releases, pamphlets, reports, transcripts, 1945-1978 (Folder 12)
    - Strategic superiority (U.S.A. vs. U.S.S.R.). Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, transcripts, 1958-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Dominican Republic. Flyers, newsletter, pamphlet, correspondence with William J. Johnson (Dominican Republic Herald) and Henry Regnery, 1949-1963 (Folder 2-3)
  - Eastern Europe. Newsletter, notes, pamphlet, press release and correspondence with Dumitru Danielopol and others, Includes typescript copy of statement by Charles J. Kersten relating to the Kersten amendment to the Mutual Security Act, and mimeographed surveys issued by the Federal Communications Commission, Foreign Broadcast Intelligence Services, 1942-1970. 1951; c. 1944 (Folder 4)
  - Economics
    - General. Biographical sketches, correspondence, notes, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, 1951-1977 (Folder 5-6)
    - Business
      - General. Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, 1951-1976 (Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence with the Allen-Bradley Company, General Electric, Gulf Oil Corp., International Business Machines Corp., Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy, National Federation of Independent Business, Noble Advertising Co., Research Institute of America, Inc., United States National Bank, J. Weingarten, Inc., 1951-1961
    - Currency. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, 1962-1979 (Folder 9)
    - Fiscal policy. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reports, transcripts, statements by Peter H. Dominick, William E. Jenner, George W. Malone, Lawrence H. Smith, Willis E. Stone, mimeographed reports by Otto Passman, Americanism or Socialism?, Robert M. Bleiberg, New York City: Decline and Fall, and New York's Big Spender, 1954-1975 (Folder 10)
    - Gold. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, mimeographed reports of George Racey Jordan, Gold and Freedom, and Robert M. Bleiberg, A New Gold Rush, 1957-1972 (Folder 11)
    - Taxation. Charts, clippings, press releases, reports, mimeographed copy of Robert M. Bleiberg, Selling the Hangman the Rope, 1951-1974 (Folder 12)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - General. Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, transcripts, and correspondence with Styles Bridges and others, 1949-1960 (Folder 13)
    - Speeches and writings, 1949-c. 1959 (Folder 14)
  - Ford, Gerald R. Clippings, newsletter and press releases, 1974-1976 (Folder 15)
  - France. Newsletters, notes, transcripts, 1961-1968 (Folder 16)
  - Germany. Biographical sketches, cartoon, correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, transcripts, 1953-1972 (Box 29)
    - General. Includes printed pamphlet of Ivone Kirkpatrick, The Inner Circle, anonymous mimeographed copy of A Visit with Chancellor Adenauer, 1953-1972 (Folder 1)
    - Berlin situation, 1959-1962 (Folder 2-3)
      - General. Includes mimeographed reports issued by Kampfgruppe gegen Unmenschlichkeit (organization) relating to the political situation in Berlin, printed pamphlet by the Press Office of the German Embassy, To Keep Berlin Free, and mimeographed statements by Styles Bridges, Thomas Dodd, and John Kennedy, 1959-1961
      - Correspondence with Thomas J. Dodd, John F. Kennedy, Joint Senate-House Republican Leadership group, 1961-1962
  - Ghana. Newsletters, pamphlets, serial issues, 1964-1967 (Folder 4)
  - Greece. Pamphlets, transcript, printed copy (pamphlet) of K.P. Gorshenin, V.S. Nesterov, A.A. Piontkovsky, M.S. Strogovich, Freedom for the Greek Democrats, 1950-1959 (Folder 5)
  - India. Newsletter, pamphlet, typescript copy of article, 1953-1974 (Folder 6)
  - Indonesia. Newsletters, and correspondence with the State Department, Public Services Division, 1958-1959 (Folder 7)
  - Iran. Biographical sketch and newsletter, 1959-1979 (Folder 8)
  - Iraq. Clipping, 1958. (Folder 9)
  - Israel. Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, correspondence with the Israeli embassy in Washington and others, 1952-1972 (Folder 10)
  - Italy (Folder 11)
    - General. Biographical statements, business cards, flyers, miscellany, newsletters, notes, press releases, transcripts, 1953-1977
    - Correspondence with the Daughters of the American Revolution, Edna Fluegel, the Italian embassy in Washington, Strom Thurmond, and others, 1960-1971